Preliminary Guide to the Washington State University Environmental Health and Safety Records 1987-1994
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
Preliminary Guide to the Washington State University Environmental Health and Safety Records
1987-1994
Washington State University Libraries, Manuscripts, Archives and Special Collections
UA1997-18
Washington State University. Environmental Health and Safety
14 Linear feet of shelf space 14 Boxes
Shipping files, contracts, and project proposals relating to the removal of hazardous waste and other WSU Environmental Health and Safety projects from 1987-1994.
Environmental Health and Safety is a non-academic service department dedicated to promoting and supporting the university’s efforts to protect human health, safety and the environment.
All boxes contain shipment files, contracts, and project proposals related to the removal of hazardous waste and other projects related to Environmental Health and Safety from 1987-1994.
This is an unprocessed collection. Any arrangement reflects either a pre-existing order from the records' creators or previous custodians, or preliminary sorting performed by staff.
Boxes 1-5 contain files from 1989-1993. Boxes 6-13 contain files from 1993-1994. Each box has an item list inside. Boxes contain subject matter files that are clearly organized.
This collection is open and available for research use.
This material was transferred to WSU Libraries' MASC by Millie Hill of Environmental Health and Safety on November 17, 1997 and retained as UA1997-18.
On Sept. 9, 2012, Ade Snider of EHS withdrew boxes 7-9 as a part of a records retention project. In July, 2010, Jason T. Sampson of EHS retrieved and reorganized boxes 6, 11-14, 16, and 19-22. The collection listing of holdings reflectes the organization
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the online catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search the catalog using these headings.
Washington State University. Environmental Health and Safety -- Records and correspondence
Washington (State); Colleges and Universities
- June 93 Rollins (Box 1)
- July 93 Rollins (Box 1)
- Sept. 93 Rollins (Box 1)
- Oct. 93 Rollins (Box 1)
- 10/6/92 ChemPro (Box 2)
- 11/19/92 Rollins (Box 2)
- 12/29/92 Ensco (Box 2)
- 1/20/94 PRS (Box 3)
- 2/27/94 Ensco (Box 3)
- 2/14/94 CSSI (Box 3)
- 1/24/94 Ensco (Box 3)
- 8/27/91 Rollins (Box 4)
- 8/2/91 Rollins (Box 4)
- 7/12/91 Rollins (Box 4)
- 4/17/91 Rollins (Box 4)
- 9/20/90 Chem Waste Mngmt (Box 4)
- 7/27/90 CSSI (Box 4)
- 5/32/90 CSSI (Box 4)
- 5/11/90 Chem Waste Mngmt (Box 4)
- 4/30/90 CSSI (Box 4)
- 4/20/90 Rollins (Box 4)
- 3/30/90 CSSI (Box 4)
- 1/17/92 Rollins (Box 5)
- 2/31/92 Ensco (Box 5)
- 6/6/91 Ensco (Box 5)
- 9/91 ETSC (Box 5)
- 91/92/93 Safety Kleen (Box 5)
- Box WITHDRAWN - 9/94 Ensco (CCR's only) (Box 5)
- 12/21/93 Ensco (Box 6)
- 10/29/93 Ensco (shipping papers MIA) (Box 6)
- 1/29/93 Rollins (Box 7)
- 3/93 EITC (Box 7)
- 4/1/93 Rollins (Box 7)
- 5/14/93 Ensco (Box 7)
- 5/18/93 ChemPro (Box 7)
- 5/2/93 Rollins (Box 7)
- 8/90 ETSC (Box 8)
- 7/25/90 Ensco (Box 8)
- 4/25/90 Ensco (Box 8)
- 4/11/90 Ensco (Box 8)
- 6/7/91 ChemPro (Box 8)
- 6/13/90 ChemPro (Box 8)
- 11/28/89 ChemPro (Box 8)
- 11/30/89 ChemPro (Box 8)
- 12/20/89 Ensco (Box 8)
- 9/14/89 Ensco (Box 8)
- 6/22/89 Ensco (Box 8)
- 3/28/89 Ensco (Box 8)
- 7/23/92 Rollins (Box 9)
- 8/21/92 Rollins (Box 9)
- Fall 92 Rollins (Comp ID# 92400 -92-2350 No Shipment papers) (Box 9)
- Box WITHDRAWN - Treatment Records 1989-5/91 (Box 9)
- Box WITHDRAWN - Treatment Records 5/93-12/91 (Box 9)
- Box WITHDRAWN - Treatment Records 1994 (Box 9)
- Box WITHDRAWN - Treatment Records 1992 (Box 9)
- Misc. CCR's 11990 -1994 Dump, Recycle, PCh etc... (Box 10)
- Box WITHDRAWN - 4/24/87 Tech Rep (Box 10)
- 1/28/87 Tech Rep (Box 10)
- 1/13/87 Tech Rep Mixed Waste (Box 10)
- 1991-1996 Safety Kleen 1996 (Box 10)
- 1/20/94 Spencer (Box 11)
- 3/1/94 Aptus-Coffeyville (Box 11)
- 3/3/94 Rollins (Box 11)
- 3/15/94 Rollins (Box 11)
- 4/19/94 Ensco (Box 11)
- 6/23/94 Rollins (Box 11)
- 9/29/94 Ensco (Box 12)
- 10/26/94 Ensco (Box 12)
- 10/14/94 Ensco (Box 12)
- 11/9/94 Spencer (Box 12)
- 12/22/94 Rollins (Box 12)
- 3/9/95 Ensco (Box WITHDRAWN)
- 4/3/95 Ensco (Box WITHDRAWN)
- 5/10/95 Rollins (Box WITHDRAWN)
- 7/28/95 Ensco (Box WITHDRAWN)
- 10/18/95 Rollins 1/17/96 Ensco (Box WITHDRAWN)
- 3/17/96 Rollins 6/14/96 Ensco (Box WITHDRAWN)
- Treatment Records 1993 (Box WITHDRAWN)
- 1989 Dangerous Waste Annual Report (Box 13)
- Employee Training Files (HW) (Box 14)
- Dangerous Waste Annual Reports 1990,91,92,93,94 (Box 15)
- Public Health: Mosquito Abatement, Termite Bids, Food Sanitation (Box 16)
- WSU Part B Permit (Box 1 of 2) (Box 17)
- WSU Part B Permit (Box 2 of 2) (Box 18)